

## **Profile**

Experienced Senior Business Analyst with a complete Master's degree in Engineering Business Management at the University of Warwick (Class of 2023) and a demonstrated history of working in Consulting and Business Management industry.

Skilled in Analytical and researches with multi-lingual abilities (English, Chinese and Japanese), strong interpersonal and communication skills with an excellent personal and telephone manner, enhanced by the ability to relate to people on all levels with various backgrounds and culture.

## **Employment History**

## Part-time analyst, Nomura Research Institute (Thailand), Bangkok

JULY 2020 - MARCH 2023

- Conducted business research and analysis for Japanese clients as Part-time analyst
- Assisted in business interviews and presentation slides making and design
- Involved in projects in manufacturing, automotive, real-estate and medical related industries

### Senior Business Analyst, Nomura Research Institute (Thailand), Bangkok

MAY 2018 - JULY 2020

- Involved in more than 20 key projects and proposals altogether of which including 2 long-run massive governmental projects
- Performed as key member representing Nomura at National Innovation
  Agency event which was attended by more than 60 governmental officers
  from all Ministries, discussing on smart logistics and agricultural improvement
  in Thai fruits
- Completed company's "global startup training" program in Japan and was elected as #1 project case presentation during the final presentation training out of 20 presenters
- Conducted market research and data collection through different methods and assisted team in analyzing stakeholder's expectations and translating key implication to strategy

## Student Assistant Program (Conference Assistant), United Nations ESCAP, Bangkok

MAY 2018 - MAY 2018

- Elected as one of Faculty representatives to take charge in the 74th session of the Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific held at the United Nations Conference Center in Thailand
- Worked alongside other representative from other leading Universities and the notable working groups from UNESCAP to facilitate the international event with the entitled theme "inequality"

## Japan Internship Program, Ministry of Economics Trade and Industry, Government of Japan (METI), Osaka

OCTOBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

• Selected as 1 of out of 15 Thailand's representatives to participate in a national internship program organized by METI, Government of Japan

#### **Details**

Bangkok Thailand (+66)85-919-0189 pakawan.pepinpe@gmail.com

### Links

Published works

LinkedIn

### Languages

**English** 

Chinese

Japanese

 Fully funded 3 month-program to seek for young talents from partnered countries to take part in revolutionizing Japanese business by joining hands with Japanese SMEs

## Case Team Assistant, The Boston Consulting Group (Thailand) Ltd, Bangkok and Khon Kaen

APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

- Assisted international team for the massive project delivered to TOP3 largest construction company in Thailand with revenue and backlog valued more than 10 Billion USD
- Developed industry and competitor analysis for internal discussions and client meetings as well as data collection and significant market research via both online and field survey for client company
- On-site interviews at client's key project worthing Millions of USD in Khon Kaen for operational and process performance and workflow evaluation

#### Intern, PricewaterhouseCoopers Consulting (Thailand) Ltd., Bangkok

OCTOBER 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

- Assisted team in the project involving one of the national Postal service company in Thailand, with most branches and distribution networks.
- Assigned translation on business reports and marketing presentation (EN-TH and TH-EN)
- Reviewed meeting contents before official meetings with clients and managed content in business reports and marketing presentation

### Education

# Master of Science in Engineering Business Management, University of Warwick, Coventry

MAY 2021 - MAY 2023

#### Attended Modules:

- International Joint Ventures, Leading Change, Lean Principles and Applications, Product Design and Development Management, Innovation, Financial Analysis and Control Systems

#### Dissertation:

- Project entitled "The extent of Industry 4.0 Digitization in Thailand and how it can help in the revolution of the Thai manufacturing industry?"
- Analytical tools: SPSS One Way ANOVA and Multiple regression

# Bachelor of Arts in Language and Culture, Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok

AUGUST 2012 - JUNE 2016

#### Attended Modules:

- Cultural Studies, Critical Theories, Mass Media Studies, International History, Cross-Cultural Management; Urban Studies, Linguistics
- Academic Second Class Honours

# Bachelor of Arts, Chinese language (Economics and Trade), Beijing Language and Culture University, Beijing

MARCH 2012 - JANUARY 2016

Attended Modules:

- Chinese Business Communications, Chinese Reading Comprehension, Fundamental Economics, Marketing Final thesis topic:
- Analysis on Thailand's major seaweed snack player "Tao Kae Noi (little boss)" and its market implication

## **Courses**

Business Analysis Program, Chulalongkorn University

JULY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Digital Marketing Program, Chulalongkorn University

JULY 2018 - JULY 2018

## References

References available upon request